Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
- RG 48.0. Polytechnic Institute of NYU / Tandon School of Engineering, 2014-2019
  - Women in STEM Newsletters, May 2021
    The Women in STEM newsletters are a product of the Tandon School of Engineerings initiative to promote women in STEM and related fields. The newsletter was first published in 2015. It includes event and program listings, application deadlines, awards, club information, history spotlights, faculty updates, and mentorship opportunities.
- RG 49.0. Abu Dhabi, 2008-2016
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2008-2016 (Box 429, Folder 15)
- RG 50. NYU Shanghai, 2022-ongoing
  - NYU Shanghai Magazine, May 2022-ongoing
    Website for the NYU Shanghai Magazine, dating back to Spring 2017. The magazine is published twice a year, and documented the lives of faculty, students, alumni, and administrators at NYU Shanghai.
  - Weekly Gazette, May 2022-ongoing
    Weekly newsletter for alumni, parents, students, and friends of NYU Shanghai.
- RG 52.0. College of Nursing, 2005-ongoing
  - College of Nursing Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the College of Nursing. Posts include obituaries, health sector news, Center for Drug Use and HIV Research, awards, scholarships, research, clinical studies, and other news.
  - College of Nursing News, May 2014-ongoing
    Website containing press releases related to news and research at the College of Nursing. News dates back to 2012.
  - College of Nursing Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the College of Nursing. Contains tweets related to nursing program open houses, admissions, advising, study abroad, student life activities, mindfulness workshops, clinical requirements, and lectures and other events.
  - Nursing Magazine, November 2016-ongoing
    Nursing Magazine is the semi annual magazine of the Rory Meyers College of Nursing. The magazine dates back to 2010. It contains messages from the Dean, college and faculty news, alumni achievements, research reports, donor spotlights, and awards.
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2005-2011 (Box 430, Folder 1-3)
- RG 53. College of Global Public Health, 2014-ongoing
  - College of Global Public Health News and Events, May 2017-June 2019
    News and events listing for the College of Global Public Health. It mostly includes news related to faculty and student research and on-campus events.
  - College of Global Public Health News and Events, November 2015-April 2019
  - Global Institute of Public Health News & Events, April 2014-May 2015
    News feed for the NYU Global Institute of Public Health (the predecessor for School of Global Public Health). The news page is made up of press releases announcing appointed deans of the Institute.
  - Passing the Torch 2015-2018, May 2020
    Passing the Torch 2015-2018 is a publication from the College of Global Public Health commemorating the first four years of the school. It contains a letter from the Dean; a history of public health at NYU; its mission and values; student, faculty, and alumni profiles; statistics about the school; departments, programs, and initiatives highlights; information about their building at 708 Broadway; and the advisory board.
  - School of Global Public Health Office of Doctoral Studies Newsletter, May 2021-May 2022
    This websites contains issues of the Office of Doctoral Studies newsletter, dating back to October 2018. The newsletter reports on student publications, presentation, fellowships, research, and conferences.
- RG 53.1. Center for Bioethics, 2014-2015
  Since its launch in 2007, the New York University Center for Bioethics has promoted a broad conception of bioethics encompassing both environmental and health ethics through conferences, workshops, public lectures, and graduate courses. Bioethics Masters students take courses from bioethicists as well from professors in the fields of dentistry, education, law, medicine, philosophy, public health, public service, and others.
  - Center for Bioethics Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Center for Bioethics. Page includes posts related to admissions, workshops, and other events.
  - Center for Bioethics Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Center for Bioethics. Tweets are related to admissions, lectures, film screenings, articles written by alumni, Arthur Caplan, and other events. Tweets date back to 2010.